Priya Laroiya

UX/UI Designer

As a designer, I find it extremely fulfilling to be able to solve problems and bring a client's idea to reality. I get a lot of satisfaction from witnessing a piece of work evolve from concept to design.

laroiya.priya59@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/priya-laroiya-b5634aa2/ in

priyalaroiya.github.io/

9873146965

Bengaluru, India 💡

Design Projects

Cuku: music app

Capstone Project – 4 months

May 2021 - August 2021

Redesigning the user experience of the music app to offer more features than the freemium model in order to attract more users by creating visually delightful interfaces while also meeting the business needs to monetize the product and create revenue.

Savr: recipe app

Design Sprint Project — 5 days

Dec 2020 - Dec 2020

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

Redesigned the Savr app to incorporate user feedback around to simplify recipes and techniques.

IKEA: Home furnishing web application

Capstone Project – 4 months

Redesigned IKEA's existing web experience to assist customers in making a smooth and hassle-free purchasing decision by gathering data. Main features have been improved to make the shopping experience more efficient.

Work Experience

Interior designer

IKEA India

July 2019 - Aug 2021

- Led mentored and aided in the redesign of shop pop-up homes on a consumer-facing platform, which resulted in exceeding our daily targets of one crore.
- Collaborated and implemented design solutions with the Scandinavian design team for YouTube AD 2019, to launch the 'Make space for everyone' campaign...
- Built vital client connections by providing design solutions that addressed needs without compromising quality or design intent, resulting in weekly sales of ten lakh rupees for each project.

Senior Visual Merchandiser

Landmark group, Homecentre

Feb 2018 - July 2019

- Executed merchandising strategies using visual design throughout in opening of 3 stores: Noida, Calcutta, Mumbai.
- Analysed customer flow every month which ensures 80% more visibility leading to 1 crore sale for consecutive 3 days.

Education

UX/UI Design Career Track

Springboard

Aug 2020 - Present

M.DES CAD/CAM

FDDI, Noida

July 2014-July 2016

Skills & Competencies

Research

Storyboarding

Wireframing

Prototyping

User interviews and testing

Team collaboration

Diligent listener and persuasive speaker

Tools

Figma

Sketch

Invision

Moqups

Illustrator

Principle

Portfolio

https://priyalaroiya.github.io/